{"answer": "following", "a": "know", "c": "said", "b": "was", "question": "What does following mean in the following sentence?\nRead the following section from the story:   [Mia   s mother] explained that they didn   t have online search engines to help them withtheir work; they could only rely on books."}
{"answer": "passage", "a": "know", "c": "passage", "b": "had", "question": "What does passage mean in the following sentence?\nAs used in the passage, what does the phrase    pitch in    mean?sac      cehemsuffercookUOW>7."}
{"answer": "think", "a": "passage", "c": "t", "b": "had", "question": "What does think mean in the following sentence?\nshe asked, wondering what they were thinking."}
{"answer": "pitch", "a": "had", "c": "passage", "b": "passage", "question": "What does pitch mean in the following sentence?\nAlso, since I had many brothers and sisters, we had to pitch in more."}
{"answer": "rich_person", "a": "have", "c": "made", "b": "made", "question": "What does have mean in the following sentence?\nI have to design a website page for mycomputer class."}
{"answer": "know", "a": "had", "c": "t", "b": "passage", "question": "What does know mean in the following sentence?\nWhen we were in middle school,we didn't even know how to use computers."}
{"answer": "be", "a": "pitch", "c": "did", "b": "said", "question": "What does were mean in the following sentence?\nWhen we were in middle school,we didn't even know how to use computers."}
{"answer": "state", "a": "know", "c": "pitch", "b": "be", "question": "What does said mean in the following sentence?\nMia said."}
{"answer": "make", "a": "passage", "c": "was", "b": "said", "question": "What does made mean in the following sentence?\nBased on this evidence, what conclusion can be made?UOW>Mia thinks new technology makes homework easier.Mia   s parents think that her homework is too easy.Mia thinks it would be more fun to work with a partner.Mia   s parents think she should have a cell phone.4."}
{"answer": "have", "a": "pitch", "c": "think", "b": "made", "question": "What does had mean in the following sentence?\nIt had been a long week-she was working on a computer project and had stayed late at school to finish her work."}
{"answer": "1 3 2 4 ", "a": "2 4 3 1 ", "c": "1 4 3 2 ", "b": "2 3 1 4 ", "question": "Identify the correct order for the following sentences: 1: What   s up, Mia?\n2: What is one way that Mia   s life is different from her mother   s?\n3: They didn   t have cell phones to text each other when they needed help   theyhad to work together at each other   s houses.\n4: We know because Mia   s mother tells her that when she was in middleschool, they didn   t even know how to use computers.o Mia uses cell phones to contact her partner, while her mother and father had to work together ateach other   s houses.\n"}
{"answer": "4 3 1 2 ", "a": "1 4 2 3 ", "c": "3 2 1 4 ", "b": "3 4 1 2 ", "question": "Identify the correct order for the following sentences: 1: When we were in middle school,we didn't even know how to use computers.\n2: But that sounds so hard!\n3: Based on this evidence, what conclusion can be made?UOW>Mia thinks new technology makes homework easier.Mia   s parents think that her homework is too easy.Mia thinks it would be more fun to work with a partner.Mia   s parents think she should have a cell phone.4.\n4: How do you know?Use evidence from the passage to support your answer.\n"}
{"answer": "time_unit", "a": "parents", "c": "leap_second", "b": "help", "question": "A(n) s is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "parent", "a": "primipara", "c": "help", "b": "mater", "question": "A(n) mother is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "activity", "a": "paperwork", "c": "coursework", "b": "spadework", "question": "A(n) work is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "genitor", "a": "mother", "c": "adoptive_parent", "b": "work", "question": "A(n) parents is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "work", "a": "labor_of_love", "c": "baby", "b": "marathon", "question": "A(n) project is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "activity", "a": "self-help", "c": "service", "b": "thanks", "question": "A(n) help is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "message", "a": "nursery_rhyme", "c": "evidence", "b": "didn", "question": "A(n) story is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "speech", "a": "work", "c": "table_talk", "b": "talk", "question": "A(n) conversation is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "machine", "a": "analog_computer", "c": "turing_machine", "b": "number_cruncher", "question": "A(n) Computers is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "school_assignment", "a": "dinner", "c": "parents", "b": "school", "question": "A(n) homework is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "educational_institution", "a": "grade_school", "c": "together", "b": "language_school", "question": "A(n) school is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "abstraction", "a": "cabotage", "c": "right_of_action", "b": "floor", "question": "A(n) rights is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "being", "a": "cell", "c": "ghetto", "b": "story", "question": "A(n) life is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "skilled_worker", "a": "roaster", "c": "chef", "b": "fry_cook", "question": "A(n) cook is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "compartment", "a": "rights", "c": "together", "b": "evidence", "question": "A(n) cell is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "party", "a": "help", "c": "ReadWorks", "b": "middle", "question": "A(n) do is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "information", "a": "symptom", "c": "proof", "b": "probable_cause", "question": "A(n) evidence is an example of a ____________."}
{"answer": "MineCraft", "a": "Penguins", "c": "Guardians of the Galaxy", "b": "Star Wars", "question": "What or who is the main subject of the article?"}
{"answer": "NN", "a": "Noun", "c": "Verb", "b": "Adjective", "question": "What part of speech is \"life\" in the following sentence:\nWhat does Mia mainly learn about in the story?UOW>how her parents methow her mother   s life differed from hershow to use computers to do homeworkhow to work in pairs3."}
{"answer": "NN", "a": "Noun", "c": "Verb", "b": "Adjective", "question": "What part of speech is \"thinks\" in the following sentence:\nBased on this evidence, what conclusion can be made?UOW>Mia thinks new technology makes homework easier.Mia   s parents think that her homework is too easy.Mia thinks it would be more fun to work with a partner.Mia   s parents think she should have a cell phone.4."}
{"answer": "NN", "a": "Noun", "c": "Verb", "b": "Adjective", "question": "What part of speech is \"work\" in the following sentence:\nReadworks Computers vs. BooksCom puters vs. BooksMia Murphy was tired when she got home from school last Friday."}
{"answer": "NN", "a": "Noun", "c": "Verb", "b": "Adjective", "question": "What part of speech is \"middle\" in the following sentence:\nWhen we were in middle school,we didn't even know how to use computers."}
